

Inter

serenadmello199@gmail.com 7276685256 Juliana sadan near B.K.S school vasia west , Mumbai, 401202, India

Date of birth 09/12/2003

Nationality Indian

Serena Dmelllo

Profile

Hello I am Serena Dmello

I'm passionate about two things: writing and psychology. Over the years, have done many internships related to marketing and psychology as marketing and psychology are interrelated to understand and influence consumer behavior. By applying principles like motivation, perception, social proof, emotion, and cognitive biases, marketers craft strategies that resonate with consumers, enhance their experience and build strong brands. I have gained knowledge and learned many skills related to writing, research, marketing, and SEO and I've had the opportunity to dive deep into both fields. Professionally, I've honed my skills while working with a company, where I've had the chance to apply my writing expertise to various projects. And I've explored my creativity through my blog, where I've shared my thoughts.

I am deeply fascinated with psychology. I'm endlessly intrigued by the complexities of human behavior and the intricacies of the mind. Understanding why people think and act the way they do has always captivated me. It's like unraveling a never-ending puzzle; each discovery brings me closer to understanding the world around me.

Employment History

Psychology inter at asmi

05/2024-06/2024

We extensively covered the topic of relationship trauma and examined a compelling case study to gain a deeper understanding of its implications. analysis

Intern at The Happiness Project, virtual

11/2023-12/2023

During my internship at The Happiness Project, which was in the field of psychology I had the opportunity to contribute to various projects and gain practical experience in the field. I was involved in conducting research, drafting reports, and assisting with project coordination. This experience allowed me to develop my research and problem-solving skills, as well as gain valuable insights into the field of psychology.

- · Contributed to research projects and report drafting
- · Assisted in project coordination
- · Developed research and problem-solving skills
- · made PPT related to psychology

Links

linkedIn
Authored a book on Wattpad
Personal blog site
blogs written during my internship
(Mobavenue)
blog written during my internship
(Mobavenue)
podcast (overwhelming regrets)
youtube

Skills

Ability to Work Under Pressure
Public Speaking
Analytical Thinking Skills
Microsoft Office
Highly responsible and reliable
Fast Learner
Complex Problem Solving
Interpersonal Communication Skills
Critical Thinking
Creative Problem Solving
Good time management
Attention to Detail
Hard Working
Active Listening
Microsoft Office Word

Mobavenue at content writer inter, Mumbai

07/2023-10/2023

Combining SEO and creative writing is key to crafting engaging, discoverable content. Effective blog writing requires knowing your audience, conducting thorough research, and structuring posts with clear headings, visuals, and anecdotes. To ensure your content is credible and informative, gather accurate information from reliable sources. Reading your work aloud and editing for clarity, coherence, and quality—focusing on grammar, flow, and consistency—enhances readability and impact. This approach balances optimization for search engines with captivating, well-researched parratives that resonate with readers.

Psychology Research Inter at Positive Mind care & Research center

01/2022-10/2023

- · Had to write research papers
- · Case study and analysis
- Collaborated with a research team to develop research proposals and prepare grant applications
- Developed a research database to store and organize data from the research project
- Drafted research papers for publication in peer-reviewed journals and presented research findings at international conferences

Psychology research inter at International Institute Of SDG'S And Public Policy Research

06/2022-11/2022

- · Gained practical experience in psychology
- · Insights into the human resources and teaching departments.
- · How research papers are done and written
- Conducted a comprehensive literature review to identify gaps in knowledge and provide recommendations for future research

volunteering at InAmigos Foundation, Mumbai

05/2022-07/2022

- Engaged in volunteering activities supporting the In amigos Foundation
- · Planting trees & saving environment
- Fund raising
- Handled customer complaints calmly and professionally, resolving customer issues in a timely manner

content writer at Writorek

09/2021-10/2021

- · Contributed to content creation projects during this internship.
- · How a content writer is and how it done
- · Mostly product reviews and editing
- Developed and maintained a content calendar to ensure timely delivery of content

Flexibility and Adaptability Critical thinking and problem solving Communication Ability to Work in a Team Self-motivation Microsoft PowerPoint Interpersonal Skills Leadership and Teamwork Leadership Skills Ability to Multitask Computer Skills **Problem Solving** Creativity **Decision Making Effective Time Management** Adaptability **Time Management** Market Research **Communication Skills Project Management Content Writing** Leadership Psychology Internship Research Analysis Teamwork

Courses

active listing at speak your mind.in 02/2023—02/2023

research psychology at International Institute of SDG's and Public Policy Research 09/2022

fundamental of digital marketing at google 06/2021

 Managed content creation and publication process, ensuring timely and accurate delivery of content

Education

Bachelor Of Arts In Psychology , Mumbai University

07/2021-06/2024

Psynergy- festival of Maanas Psychology associated of D.G Ruparel college

· social media volunteer

Athena - event of Philosophy cult, department of Philosophy of D.G.Ruparel College

- · content writing volunteering
- · event volunteering

HSC, Thomas Baptist Junior college

06/2019-08/2021

SSC, Canossa Convent Girls High School

03/2018-03/2019